A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 2 FA1390
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants and Subject Files, 1964-1967, 1969, 1971-2004; 1; 23.91 Cubic Feet 49 legal document boxes and 1 flat file
  - 91-550, Xi'an Medical University, Cancer, Virus, and Epidemology, 1991-1999 (Box 25, Folder 204)
  - 92-566, Xi'an Medical University, Continuing Medical Education, 1992-1999 (Box 25, Folder 205-206)
  - 81-400, Hunan Medical University, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1981-1999 (Box 26, Folder 207)
  - 82-410, Hunan Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1982-1999 (Box 26, Folder 208)
  - 83-417, Hunan Medical University, Production of Video Tapes, 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 209)
  - 83-420, Hunan Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1983-1991, 1993-1999 (Box 26, Folder 210)
  - 85-435, Hunan Medical College, Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 211)
  - 86-444, Hunan Medical College, Endowment Fund for Nursing Education, 1986-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 212)
  - 86-447, Hunan Medical College, Endowment Fund for Postgraduate Training, 1986-1999 (Box 26, Folder 213)
  - 86-450, Hunan Medical College, Endowment Fund for Public Health, 1986-1998 (Box 26, Folder 214)
  - 87-470, Hunan Medical College, Endowment Fund for Training of Technical and Administrative Personnel, 1987-1998 (Box 27, Folder 215)
  - 88-482, Hunan Medical University, Endowment, General Institutional Development, 1988-1998 (Box 27, Folder 216)
  - 89-516, Hunan Medical University, Biomedical Research, 1989-1997 (Box 27, Folder 217)
  - 90-529, Hunan Medical University, Interdisciplinary Program/Nasopharyneal Cancer, 1990-1998 (Box 27, Folder 218-221)
  - 92-556, Hunan Medical University, Substance Abuse Program, 1991-1997 (Box 28, Folder 222)
  - 88-504, Jiujiang Medical College, Fund to Reform Medical Education, 1988-1994 (Box 28, Folder 223)
  - 89-520, Jiujiang Medical College, Reform Medical Education, 1989-1994 (Box 28, Folder 224)
  - 91-541, Jiujiang Medical College, Clinical Skills Program, 1990-1999 (Box 28, Folder 225)
  - 91-544, Jiujiang Medical College, Medical Library, 1991-1997 (Box 28, Folder 226)
  - 80-389, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Endowment for Research & Research Planning, 1980-1983, 1985-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 28, Folder 227)
  - 80-390, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Endowment for Staff Development, 1980-1999 (Box 28, Folder 228)
  - 80-391, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Repairs and Architectural Consultation, 1979-1981, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 229)
  - 80-392, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Endowment for Library, 1980-1999 (Box 29, Folder 230)
  - 82-414-12, 87-467-3, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Huanguang, Jin, 1986-1989, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 231)
  - 83-417, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Audio-Visual Meeting, 1987 October 19-23, 1987-1989 (Box 29, Folder 232-233)
  - 85-435, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 234)
  - 86-445, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Endowment Fund for Nursing Education, 1986-1999 (Box 29, Folder 235)
  - 86-448, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Endowment Fund for Postgraduate Training, 1986-1999 (Box 29, Folder 236)
  - 86-451, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Endowment Fund for Medical Technology Development, 1986-1999 (Box 29, Folder 237)
  - 86-452, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Public Health Development, 1986, 1988, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 238)
  - 87-467, 96-651, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), School of Nursing, Hauping, Liu, 1995-2002 (Box 30, Folder 239)
  - 88-483, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Endowment, General Institutional Development, 1988-1999 (Box 30, Folder 240)
  - 89-513, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Biomedical Instrumentation, 1989-1990, 1992-1996, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 241)
  - 89-518, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Biomedical Research, 1989-1993 (Box 30, Folder 242)
  - 89-521, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Neurological Disorders Research Program, 1989-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 243)
  - 90-524, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Interdisciplinary Program/Medical Genetics, 1989-1995, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 244)
  - 90-531, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Clinical Epidemiology-Quality Assurance, 1990-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 245)
  - 91-546, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Roof Renovation, 1980, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 246)
  - 92-553, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 75th Anniversary Academic Activities, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 247)
  - 92-553, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 75th Anniversary Academic Activities, Publications, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 248)
  - 92-574, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Medical Research, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 249)
  - 93-581, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Enrollment Transition, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 250)
  - 92-582, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Hepatitis Virus, 1992-2000 (Box 31, Folder 251-254)
  - 93-593, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC)/Beijing Medical University, Fellowship Program, 1993-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 32, Folder 255)
  - 94-602, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), M.D.-Ph.D Program, 1994-1995, 1997-2003 (Box 32, Folder 256)
  - 94-604, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), General Institutional Development, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 257)
  - 94-608, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Medical Information Network, 1992, 1994-2001 (Box 32, Folder 258)
  - 95-612, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Biomedical Engineering's Program, 1995, 1997-2001 (Box 32, Folder 259)
  - 95-616, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC)/Beijing Medical University, Clinical Education, 1995-1996, 1998-2003 (Box 32, Folder 260)
  - 95-617, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Medical Genetics, 1995-2001 (Box 32, Folder 260)
  - 95-618, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Nursing Education, 1995-1999, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 262)
  - 97-665, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), School of Nursing, Nursing Fellowshiip, 1997-1999, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 263)
  - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 75th Anniversary, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 264)
  - 81-402, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Endowment for Staff Development, 1981-1999 (Box 33, Folder 265)
  - 82-412, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Endowment for Medical Research, 1982-1995, 1997, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 266)
  - 83-422, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Endowment for Medical Library, 1983-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 33, Folder 267)
  - 85-435, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 268)
  - 86-456, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Endowment Fund for Nursing Education Development, 1986-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 33, Folder 269)
  - 86-460, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Postgraduate Medical Education Development, 1986-1999 (Box 33, Folder 270)
  - 86-464, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Endowment Fund for Public Health Development, 1986-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 34, Folder 271)
  - 87-473, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Endowment Fund for Training Technical Personnel, 1987-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 34, Folder 272)
  - 88-486, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Endowment, General Institutional Development, 1988-1999 (Box 34, Folder 273)
  - 90-539, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Clinical Skills Program, 1991-1996 (Box 34, Folder 274-275)
  - 90-539, 90-540, Clinical Skills Program, General Information, 1991-1994, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 276)
  - 91-539, University of Massachusetts, Clinical Skills Program, PRC Trip, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 277)
  - 91-539, Clinical Skills Program Workshop, 1992 May 20-June 20, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 278)
  - 91-539, Clinical Skills Program, Payments-University of Massachusetts, Travel Expenses, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 279)
  - 91-539, Clinical Skills Program, Stillman, Paula L., PRC Trip, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 280)
  - 91-539, Clinical Skills Program, PRC Training Trip, 1993 July-August, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 281)
  - 91-539, Clinical Skills Program, PRC Training Trip, 1993 July-August, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 281A)
    Restricted-personal information
  - 91-539, Eastern Virginia Medical School Clinical Skills Program, PRC Training Trip, 1994 May-June, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 282)
  - 91-539, Medical School of Pennsylvania/Clinical Skills Program, PRC Training Trip, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 283)
  - 91-539, Clinical Skills Program, Stillman, Paula L. and Wong, Youde Trip, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 284)
  - 91-539, 91-540, Eastern Virginia Medical School, Clinical Skills Program, Agreement/Contract, 1992, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 285)
  - 91-542, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Clinical Skills Program, 1990-1998 (Box 35, Folder 286)
  - Clinical Skills Manuscript, Sawyer, William D. and Stillman, Paula L., 1992, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 287)
  - Clinical Skills Program, Article Submitted to the New England Journal of Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 288)
  - Stillman, Paula L., Recommendations, etc., 1991-1996 (Box 36, Folder 289)
  - 92-557, West China University of Medical Sciences (WCUMS), Rural Community mental Health Care, 1991-1998 (Box 36, Folder 290)
  - 81-401, Shanghai Medical University, Endowment for Staff Development, 1981, 1983-1997 (Box 36, Folder 291)
  - 82-411, Shanghai Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1982-1999 (Box 36, Folder 292)
  - 83-421, Shanghai Medical University, Library Endowment, 1982-1998 (Box 37, Folder 293)
  - 85-435, Shanghai Medical University, Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985-1986 (Box 37, Folder 299)
  - 86-455, Shanghai Medical University, Endowment Fund for Nursing Education Development, 1986-1999 (Box 37, Folder 300)
  - 86-459, Shanghai Medical University, Endowment Fund for Postgraduate Medical Education Development, 1986-1999 (Box 37, Folder 301)
  - 86-463, Shanghai Medical University, Endowment Fund for Public Health Development, 1986-1999 (Box 37, Folder 302)
  - 87-467-2, Shanghai Medical University, Fellowships, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 303)
  - 87-471, Shanghai Medical University, Endowment Fund for Training Technical Personnel, 1987-1999 (Box 37, Folder 304)
  - 88-484, Shanghai Medical University, Endowment Fund for General Institutional Development, 1988-1999 (Box 37, Folder 305)
  - 88-506, Shanghai Medical University, Biomedical Research, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 306)
  - 90-527, Shanghai Medical University, Kidney Research Program, 1989-1997 (Box 38, Folder 307-309)
  - 81-399, China Medical University, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1981-1999 (Box 38, Folder 310)
  - 82-409, China Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1981-1982, 1984-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 311)
  - 83-419, China Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1999 (Box 38, Folder 312)
  - 85-435, China Medical University, Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 313)
  - 86-454, China Medical University, Endowment Fund for Nursing Education Development, 1986-1999 (Box 39, Folder 314)
  - 86-458, China Medical University, Endowment Fund for Postgraduate Medical Education Development, 1986-1994, 1996-1999 (Box 39, Folder 315)
  - 86-462, China Medical University, Endowment Fund for Public Health Development, 1986, 1988-1999 (Box 39, Folder 316)
  - 87-469, China Medical University, Endowment Fund for Training Technical Personnel, 1987-1999 (Box 39, Folder 317)
  - 88-481, China Medical University, Endowment Fund for General Institutional Development, 1988-1999 (Box 39, Folder 318)
  - 91-537, China Medical University, Emergency Medical Program, 1990-1998 (Box 39, Folder 319-320)
  - 91-537, China Medical University, Emergency Medical Program, 1990-1998 (Box 40, Folder 321)
  - 91-547, China Medical University, Assessment of Cognitive Skills, 1991-1999 (Box 40, Folder 322-324)
  - 92-564, China Medical University, Supplemental Medical Research Fund, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 325)
  - 96-647, China Medical University, Comprehensive Final Exam in Medicine, 1996-2000 (Box 40, Folder 326)
  - 96-654, China Medical University, Medical English, 1996-2001 (Box 41, Folder 327)
  - Balloon Catheters, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 328)
  - Basic Benefits Package, 1987-1989, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 329)
  - Bernardin, Joseph Cardinal, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 330)
  - Biomedical Science, Clinical Trials, Hoofnagle Investigation, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 331)
  - Biomedical Science, Cost Effectiveness (Box 41, Folder 332)
  - Biomedical Science, The Future, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 333)
  - Biomedical Science, International, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 334)
  - Biomedical Science Literacy, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 335)
  - Biomedical Science, National Institutes of Health (NIH), 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 336)
  - Biomedical Science, Research, 1984, 1988, 1990-1996 (Box 41, Folder 337-338)
  - Biomedical Science, Research, 1984, 1988, 1990-1996 (Box 42, Folder 339)
  - Biomedical Science and Public Attitudes, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 340)
  - Biomedical Scientific Advancement, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 341)
  - Biomedical Scientific Earmarks, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 342)
  - Biotechnology, 1990-1995 (Box 42, Folder 343)
  - Board Certification, 1986, 1989-1990, 1992, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 344)
  - Boxing, Brain Injury, 1983, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 345)
  - Dartmouth Medical School, Board of Overseers, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 346)
  - Deanship, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 347)
  - Death, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 348)
  - Dementia, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 349)
  - Department of Defense Graduate Medical Education Advisory Committee, Summary Report, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 350)
  - Devices, 1992-1994 (Box 42, Folder 351)
  - Diabetes, 1990, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 352)
  - Dietary Supplement, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 353)
  - Dinosaurs, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 354)
  - Direct Consumer Advertising, 1988, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 355)
  - Disabled, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 356)
  - Diseases, 1989-1991, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 357)
  - DNA, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 358)
  - Doe vs. AMA, et. al., 1989 (Box 42, Folder 359)
  - Drug Abuse, 1986, 1988-1994 (Box 43, Folder 360-363)
  - Drug Approval Process, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 364)
  - Drug Costs, 1989, 1991-1995 (Box 43, Folder 365)
  - Drug Development, 1993-1995 (Box 43, Folder 366)
  - Drugs, Off Label Uses, 1982, 1987, 1989-1996 (Box 44, Folder 367)
  - Drug Pricing, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 368)
  - Drug Testing, Physicians, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 369)
  - Economy, Federal Budget, 1988-1989, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 370)
  - Economy, Foreign Investments, 1991, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 371)
  - Economy, Taxes, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 372)
  - Economy, Trade Balance, 1987, 1989-1990, 1993, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 373)
  - Economy, U. S. Economy, 1987-1990, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 374)
  - Economy, U. S. Economy: Budget, Trade Debt, Deficit, 1987-1993, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 375-377)
  - Education, 1993-1995 (Box 44, Folder 378)
  - Educational Commission for Foreign Medical Graduates (ECFMG), 1993-1995 (Box 44, Folder 379)
  - Effectiveness Research, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 380)
  - Elderly, 1987, 1989-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 381)
  - Environment, 1989-1993 (Box 45, Folder 382)
  - Embryo Research, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 383)
  - Epidemics Illegitimacy, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 384)
  - Epstein-Barr Virus, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 385)
  - Euthanasia, 1988-1995 (Box 45, Folder 389)
  - Euthanasia: Right to Live, Die, Health Care, 1984, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 387)
  - Rationing Healthcare, 1969, 1975, 1977, 1979-1984, 1987-1991, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 391)
  - Rationing Healthcare, 1969, 1975, 1977, 1979-1984, 1987-1991, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 392-393)
  - RBRVS, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 394)
  - Recredentialing Physician, 1987-1988, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 395)
  - Religion, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 396)
  - Reports: Medical Education, Science Meeting, and Others, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 397)
  - Research! America, 1993-1995 (Box 46, Folder 398)
  - Resident Work Hours & Conditions, 1987-1992 (Box 46, Folder 399)
  - Risks, 1990, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 400)
  - RU-486, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 401)
  - Rural Health Care, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 402)
  - Sammons, James H., 1984, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 403)
  - Scientific Integrity, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 404)
  - Scientific Misconduct, 1989-1996 (Box 46, Folder 405)
  - Scientific Misconduct, 1989-1996 (Box 47, Folder 406-407)
  - Self-Referral, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 408)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 409)
  - Sexuality, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 410)
  - Sexually Transmitted Diseases (STD), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 411)
  - Student Debt, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 412)
  - Subacute Care, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 413)
  - Suicide, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 414)
  - Surrogacy, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 415)
  - Teaching, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 416)
  - Technologies, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 417)
  - Technology Assessment, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 418)
  - Technology: In Vitro Fertilization, 1984-1988, 1991-1995 (Box 47, Folder 419)
  - Telemedicine, 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 420)
  - Therapeutic Substitution, 1982-1989 (Box 47, Folder 421)
  - Therapeutic Substitution, 1982-1989 (Box 48, Folder 422)
  - Tobacco, 1984-1992, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 423-425)
  - Triplicate Issue, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 426)
  - Tuberculosis, 1981, 1986, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 427)
  - Tuberculosis, 1992-1995 (Box 49, Folder 428)
  - Twins, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 429)
- Members and Officers Files, 1943, 1954-1957, 1960, 1962-1964, 1966-2003; 2; 12.24 Cubic Feet 26 legal document boxes
  - Cramer, Mary Ann, Secretary of the Board, 1964, 1966, 1974-1990, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 430)
  - Hogness, John R., General, 1967-1971, 1974, 1976, 1983-1992, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 431)
  - Hogness, John R., Nominating Committee, Chairman, 1954-1957, 1970, 1974, 1981, 1984, 1986-1990, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 432)
  - Hogness, John R., China Medical Board (CMB) Trips, 1971, 1981-1984, 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 433)
  - Hogness, John R., Retirement Dinner, 1992 December 7, 1990, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 434)
  - Manning, Bayless A., General, 1972, 1974-1981, 1984, 1986-1994, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 435)
  - Manning, Bayless A., Curriculum Vitae and Elections, 1971-1972, 1975, 1978-1987, 1992-1993, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 436)
  - Manning, Bayless A., China Medical Board (CMB) Trips, 1975, 1979, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 437)
  - Manning, Bayless A., China Medical Board (CMB) Trips, 1985-1986, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 438)
  - Manning, Bayless A., China Medical Board (CMB) Trip, Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) 75th-Leaders Meeting, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 439)
  - Ongley, Patrick A., Election Letters, Resignation Letter, and Death Announcement, 1976-1978, 1980, 1982-1985, 1988-1991, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 440)
  - Ongley, Patrick A., Deceased Notification, 1998 March 11, 1998-1999 (Box 50, Folder 441)
  - Sawyer, William D., Awards, 1996-1998 (Box 50, Folder 442)
  - Wescoe, W. Clarke, Curriculum Vitae and Elections, 1960, 1962, 1967-1968, 1970-1971, 1973, 1976, 1979, 1981-1990, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 443)
  - Wescoe, W. Clarke, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 444)
  - Evans, John R., 1981 (Box 50, Folder 445)
  - Gandasoebrata, Rawito, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 446)
  - Herrera, Florentino, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 447)
  - Huang, Chia-ssu, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 448)
  - Kwon, E. Hyock, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 449)
  - Park, Hyung Jong, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 450)
  - Peng, Meng-Tsung, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 451)
  - Preston, Peter, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 452)
  - Santoso, Rachmat, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 453)
  - Somasundaram, K., 1981 (Box 50, Folder 454)
  - Sunwanik, Romsai, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 455)
  - Virauvatti, Vikit, 1981-1983 (Box 50, Folder 456)
  - Wyrgatsch, Jean H., 1981 (Box 50, Folder 457)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, 2002 January-February (Box 50, Folder 458-459)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, 2002 March-December-2003 January (Box 51, Folder 460-470)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, 2003 February-December (Box 52, Folder 471-481)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Hong Kong Trip, 2000 September 9-October 10 (Box 52, Folder 482)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Board Meeting, Presidential Committee Meeting, Hong Kong and Medical Education Review, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 483)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Trustee-Grantee Meeting, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 484)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, President's Council, Hong Kong, 2000 September 11 (Box 53, Folder 485)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Board of Trustees Meeting, 2000 September 13-14, 1957-1958, 1962, 1964, 1969, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 486)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Xi'an Medical University Conference, 2000 September 17-18 (Box 53, Folder 487)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Ningxia Medical College Conference, 2000 September 18-21, 1999-2000 (Box 53, Folder 488)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Kumming Conference on Medical Education, 2000 September 21-24 (Box 53, Folder 489)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Educational Review, 2000 September 24-October 4 (Box 53, Folder 490)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, West China University of Medical Sciences 90th Anniversary Celebration, 2000 October 4 (Box 53, Folder 491)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip Thank Yous, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 492)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Asia-China Trip, 2001 January 10-February 5, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 493)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Asia Trip, 2001 January 10-February 5 (Box 53, Folder 494)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, NMC, Maternal Child Health, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 495)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, ResearchAmerica, Board-Executive Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 496)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Hong Kong Meeting, 2000 September 7-October 10, 1998-2000 (Box 54, Folder 497-498)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Kumming Meeting, 2000 September 21 (Box 54, Folder 499)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy & Buchanan, Robert, China Trip, 1999 September 10-October 2 (Box 54, Folder 500)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 501)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Trip, 1998 September-October, 1999 April-May (Box 54, Folder 502-503)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Trip: Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Hangzhou, & Beijing, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 504)
  - Buchanan, Robert, Trip to China, 1998 September, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 505)
  - Trustee Trip, 1998 November 4-20 (Box 55, Folder 506-507)
  - DeBing, Wang, Visit the China Medical Board, 1999 December 7 (Box 55, Folder 5008)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 509)
  - College of Integrated Science and Technology (CISAT), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 510)
  - Dartmouth Medical School Board of Overseers, General, 1993-1996 (Box 55, Folder 511-512)
  - Dartmouth Medical School Board of Overseers, General, 1993-1996 (Box 56, Folder 513)
  - Dartmouth Medical School Board of Overseers, Lunch with Bob Ferguson and Gordon McLeod, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 514)
  - Fairview National Institute on Media and the Family, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 515)
  - First St. Paul's Education, Elders Committee, 1980, 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 516)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, 2002 June 24-July 14 (Box 56, Folder 517-518)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, Hangzhou Visit, 2002 June 24-July 14 (Box 56, Item 517)
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), Beijing, 2002 June 27-29 (Box 56, Folder 519)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, China Medical University, 2002 July 2-3 (Box 56, Folder 520)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, China Trip, Dupei, Liu, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 521)
  - Global Alliance for Medical Education, Conference, 2002 June, 2001-2002 (Box 57, Folder 522)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Board Meeting, 2002 June 4 (Box 57, Folder 523)
  - Schwarz, M. Roy, Board Meeting, Presentation to the Board, 2002 June 4 (Box 57, Folder 524)